all right guys now they understand the basics of inheritance now I want to talk
好吧， 现在他们明白了 现在我想谈谈 继承的基础知识
to you guys about multiple inheritance so this is basically a way where we can inherit or get stuff from more than one
对你们说多重继承 所以这基本上是我们可以做到的一种方式 从多个人那里继承或获取东西
class so we can actually inherit from like three different classes if we want
所以我们 实际上 可以 继承 如果我们想要，就像三个不同的类
so right now I'm just going to be showing you guys two but the concept is
所以现在我就是 这样 向你们两个展示， 但概念是
the same no matter how many you use so let's go ahead and make some simple
同样的 不管 有多少你用这么 让我们继续 前进， 使 一些简单的
classes that we can inherit from and might as well since it's always fun to
我们可以继承的类和 不妨，因为它总是很有趣
pretend we're making on a little computer game so I'll make like um Mario
假装我们正在做 一点点 电脑游戏，所以 我会像 马里奥一样
like if you ever played Mario on Nintendo so what's one function that
就像你曾经玩过马里奥一样 任天堂所以这是一个功能
Mario can do will say that he can move around so move himself around and we'll just make this printout something like I
马里奥可以做到 会说他可以搬家 周围所以移动 自己，我们会 只是让这个 打印输出 像我一样
am I don't know moving whatever who cares alright so he can move around
我不知道移动任何人 关心好， 所以他可以四处走动
something simple anything you know this is just an
简单的事 你知道的任何事情只是一个
example so another class I want to make is one called shroom so we already know
例如我要做的另一个类 是一个叫做shroom的人， 所以我们已经知道了
that whenever Mario eats a mushroom or maybe he jumps on it what does he do you
每当 马里奥吃蘑菇或蘑菇时 也许他跳过它，他对你做了什么
can't jump on him because why would that do anything he can't eat him because
不能跳他，因为为什么会这样 做任何他不能吃他的事，因为
they're huge almost the size of him huh I really thought about that well in this tutorial we're going to say that he eats
他们的体型几乎与他差不多 我真的很想 过这个 教程我们要说他吃了
the shroom and probably should name it mushroom because these rooms make them I
shroom可能应该命名 蘑菇， 因为这些房间让我
don't know like sound like a druggie or something but whenever he eats shrooms
不知道听起来像药物或药物 什么， 但每当他吃shrooms
goes now I am big and this just because formatting and all right so we have two different classes right here each of
现在我很大 ，这只是因为 格式化，所以我们有两个 每个人都有不同的班级
them have a function in them we have a Mario class and he can move around all
他们有一个功能， 我们有一个 马里奥类，他 都 可以走动
Mario's can move around and we also have a shroom class that whenever heats a
马里奥可以四处走动，我们也有 一个shroom课，每当加热一个
mushroom he grows into big Mario so now what I want to do is I want to make a
蘑菇他现在变成了大马里奥 我想要做的就是我想 打一个
class that can inherit from both of these things so we're going to make a
类， 可以从两者 的 继承 这些东西所以我们要做 一个
special class called big mario and we're going to create an
特殊班叫 大 马里奥 ，我们要创造一个
object from this class whenever mario eats a mushroom now it would be kind of
每当马里奥来自这个类的对象 吃蘑菇 现在将是一种
stupid to rewrite these functions over and over again for big mario since we already wrote them one time so instead
愚蠢的重写这些功能 从我们开始 ，再为大马里奥 已经写过一次了
of having to write or rewrite a bunch of stuff over and over what I'm going to do
必须写或重写一堆 一遍又一遍我要做的事情
is I'm just going to inherit these real quick so I'm going to inherit from Mario
我只是要继承这些真实的东西 快， 所以我要 继承 马里奥
and also shroom so what this does is whenever we create an object from big Mario it already has all the
这也是为了避免它 每当 我们 从big 创建 一个对象 时 马里奥它已经拥有 的 一切
functionality of regular Mario and also shroom saves us from rewriting a whole bunch of crap now check this out here's
常规马里奥的功能也 shroom使我们无法重写整体 一堆垃圾现在检查 这里
another thing that I should probably teach you right now this big Mario class
我应该做的另一件事 现在教你这个大马里奥课程
has two functions in it even though we can't see them they're there because we
即使我们有两个功能 看不到他们 ，他们在那里，因为我们
inherited them however any time you make a class in Python you see that little
无论你做什么，都会继承它们 Python中的一个类， 你看到的很少
red line right there it says ok you pretty much need to have something in this class so I don't know that's just
红线就在那里它说 你好 非常需要有 东西 这堂课所以我不知道那是 公正的
some so you don't get a syntax error so whenever you need to write something but
一些这样你就不会得到一个语法错误 等等 每当你需要 写东西但是
it's just kind of like a blank line that you don't want to add any functionality
它就像一条空白线 你不想 添加任何功能
to it you can just write the word pass what pass means essentially like I said
你可以写下 单词 pass 什么通行证基本上就像我说的那样
is if you need a line but you don't want it to actually do anything like print out anything or change your code at all
如果你需要一条线，但你不想要 它实际上做什么 像打印 出任何东西， 或 更改您的代码 在所有
just write pass and it'll fix some it'll pretty much handle the syntax error so you don't get any exceptions but also
只是写传递，它会解决 一些问题 几乎处理语法错误 等等 你也没有任何例外
allow you to I don't know it's like just look at it you guys can see it's how do
让你，我不知道它就像是 看看它们你们可以看到 它是怎么做的
how do I explain how something does nothing kind of a riddle but I just
我该如何解释某些事情的作用 什么都不是一个 谜，但我只是
tried it and I probably just failed at it so now let's create an object from this big Mario class so BM equals big
尝试过，我可能只是失败了 它现在让我们创建一个对象 这个大 马里奥课程让BM等于大
Mario and of course now what we can do is we can call all his normal functions
马里奥，当然 现在我们能做什么 我们可以称他所有的正常功能
so we can call move look at that it pops right up so even though we didn't
所以我们可以调用move看它弹出 就这样， 即使我们没有
explicitly write any functions in here since we inherited from this Mario class
在这里显式写任何函数 因为我们继承了 这个马里奥班
we inherited the function move and we can also call what else did we inherit
我们继承了函数move和我们 还可以调用我们继承的其他内容
eat shroom check this out pretty frickin cool so another reason
吃shroom检查这个 漂亮的frickin 很酷的 另一个原因
that you might use this is let's say you wanted on I think whenever Mario like jumps on a flower he can shoot fire out
你可能会 说 ，你可以使用 它 通缉 我 觉得只要 喜欢马里奥 跳上一朵他可以射出的花
of his stomach this I never really like thought about this stuff until I'm like
这是我从不喜欢的胃 想到这个东西，直到我喜欢
trying to explain it hopefully you guys just played the game before also I'm
试图解释 它 希望 你们 我 之前只玩过游戏
going to sound like a idiot so whenever he jumps up whenever he
要听起来像 一个 白痴 所以无论什么时候他都会跳起来
jumps on a mushroom he grows in whenever he jumps on a flower he can shoot fire
跳上他随时都长大的蘑菇 他跳的一朵花，他可以拍 火
out of its stomach so if you wanted to like make a fire class then you could do
如果你愿意的话 ， 从胃里出来 比如 做一个火课，那你就可以做
that as well and also inherit from Mario so of course instead of having the right
这也和 也马里奥继承 所以当然不是拥有 正确 的
move move move the function three different times just inherit from it and boom so that's another practical example
移动移动功能三 不同的时代只是 继承它和 繁荣，这是另一个实际的例子
of when you would use inheritance but for now I am probably going to not play Mario because they would drive myself
什么时候你 会使用继承 但是 现在我 可能不打 马里奥，因为他们会 自己开车
crazy I'm going to do anything else thank as for watching don't forget
疯了我还要 做其他事 感谢 观看不要忘记
subscribe and I'll see you guys next time
订阅，我接下来会见到你们 时间